okay so this says solve for x if you
want to try this on your own positive
because I'm going to solve it in three
two one for the first step let's copy it
down and then next let's multiply both
sides by 10. on left hand side this 10
and this 10 will cancel each other out
and on the right hand side this will
just be 10 x to the 21st next let's
subtract 10x the 21st from both sides
let's bring this down and 1X to the 21
minus 10x to the 21 is equal to negative
9 x to the 21 and the right hand side is
now equal to zero from here let's factor
out the greatest common factor it's
going to be x to the 21. now x to the 21
times what gives us x to the 22 that's X
that will bring down the subtract then x
to the 21 times what gives us 9x to the
21. well that's going to be 9. here we
can set each of these equal to zero x to
the 21 equals 0 or x minus 9 equals zero
for this one if we take the 21st root of
both sides we get x equals zero and for
this one if we add 9 to both sides we
get x equals nine and these are the
solutions to the equation how exciting